{
    "id": "3b46516735be4a779a426fb4e7e163e4",
    "title": "Modification of Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are ............................ a nuisance.",
            "description": "We can use quite or rather before an article + singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce1c3bf1a14344039804a699951d6565"
        },
        {
            "question": "The film was ..................................",
            "description": "We use rather before article + singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "a rather success",
                "rather a success",
                "rather success"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f730f60fb83c47668bb51dee204407af"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... a singer is he?",
            "description": "Before a singular countable noun we can use a quantifier with of. ",
            "answers": [
                "How much",
                "How much of a",
                "How much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c64bbceea947456ea4f9082fd4adb43f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think he is .................................",
            "description": "We can use a quantifier with of before a singular countable noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "bit of a fool",
                "a bit of a fool",
                "a bit fool"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e26c913edf6b45da98d84393947aec6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ................................... than a party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more of an informal meeting",
                "more an informal meeting",
                "more of informal meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "16942ea5dc154b1c950e6a311c98a8ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ................................ politician than an activist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more a",
                "more of a",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a03b7fdfc304a19a28b881036d2b67c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .............................. an intellectual.",
            "description": "We can use a quantifier with of before a singular countable noun.  A lot is not used in the structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "a lot of",
                "very much of",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "284cb15a4949437986c853c0e9314389"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. do you want a holiday?",
            "description": "Questions about degree are asked with how much.",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How well",
                "How much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3fa9bdd522e74ce49005c4dd812efffc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You made ................................ mistakes.",
            "description": "Quite a few has a similar meaning to rather a lot.",
            "answers": [
                "rather a lot",
                "quite a few",
                "quite few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74d19ae3405f43428dfcabb8329eaa5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ............................. people who spoke German.",
            "description": "We use few with countable nouns we use little with uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "rather few",
                "rather little",
                "very little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99e782fdf9704778b89c8db7d55af3fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ate ................................ meat.",
            "description": "Too much can be modified by much and rather. ",
            "answers": [
                "much too much",
                "quite too much",
                "rather too much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c802350ddb614c12bd757cf97b7ca6d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We do ............................. of business in China.",
            "description": "A lot can be modified by quite and rather. ",
            "answers": [
                "quite a lot",
                "quite lot",
                "much a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac3a007deec1469cb3b81b73b1d3785f"
        }
    ]
}